I'm at my cutest right now.
I'm the cutest thing you've ever dumped me for.
This is how a girl strikes back.
BGM
You may have already noticed
You are me, you're so cute right now
You started it and you didn't finish it
Oh, my God, that makes me cry.
I can't believe you turned off my notifications.
I just got a message from a friend.
She says you've been in touch too much. You're the one who made her a fan.
I don't even care anymore, because right now.
I'm the cutest girl you've ever dumped.
I have the biggest crush on you in the history of my life.
It's the cutest thing I've ever seen.
I recommend you look at it. It's a counterattack.
🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이
As you can imagine, right after a heartbreak.
You're so cute, you're all messed up with tears
You made me cry
It was a messy goodbye.
What's that? I'm gonna cry.
You said it was something only you two knew.
You said only the two of you knew the story.
How did she know, too?
I wish you hadn't doubted me.
I wish you hadn't made her think I was glad she doubted you.
I liked her.
Being rejected by you made me the cutest girl alive.
In fact, I'm grateful to be the cutest.
Hey, why?
She said he got prettier.
Hey, listen.
I'm the cutest thing since you dumped me.
I'm the most beautiful girl in the history of my life.
The cutest crush ever.
Admit it. This is how a girl strikes back. Admit it, this is a damsel in distress.
I'm the cutest thing you've ever seen.
I'm the cutest thing you've ever dumped me for.
I'm the cutest thing in the world right now
I'm the cutest thing since you dumped me
This is how a girl strikes back.
You've probably noticed by now.
Maybe, but I'll tell you.
I'm so cute right now.
You started it and you didn't finish it.
That's so cute, I'm gonna cry.
I can't believe you turned off my notifications.
I got a call from a friend.
She says you've been in touch with her too much because you've been making her a fan.
I don't even care anymore, because right now, being dumped by you is the cutest thing ever.
I'm the cutest crush ever. Cutest cutest cutest cutest cutest cutest.
Admit it... this is how a girl strikes back.
It's just after a heartbreak.
You're so cute, you're all messed up with tears.
You made me cry, but it was just a quick goodbye.
What's that? I'm gonna cry. You're so cute!
She said it was a story only the two of them knew.
How did she know too?
I didn't want her to think I was glad we broke up.
I liked her.
I became the cutest girl ever after you dumped me.
You dumped me and made me the cutest girl alive.
Thank you rather. I became the cutest.
Tell him. Tell him he's become cute.
Listen.
I'm the cutest since you dumped me. I have the biggest crush of all time.
I'm the cutest! Admit it! This is what a girl learns!
I'm the cutest thing ever You dumped me and I'm the cutest thing ever
-I'm the cutest thing in the world right now
I'm the cutest thing in the world right now
I'm the cutest thing you've ever dumped me for
That's how a girl strikes back.
You may have already noticed. In case you haven't noticed by now.
But I have to tell you, I'm looking pretty darn cute right now.
I can't believe you started it and you didn't finish it.
Oh, my God, you're gonna make me cry. That's so cute.
I can't believe you turned off my notifications.
I heard from a friend.
She said you've been in touch too much, that you're a fan.
I don't care anymore. But now...
Well, now that you've dumped me, I'm the cutest thing in the world.
The most flirtatious skin tour I've ever been on.
I'm the cutest thing ever
Admit it... you're a damsel in distress.
You started it, and you didn't finish it.
As one would expect, right after a heartbreak...
You're so cute, all messed up with tears
You made me cry
It was a messy goodbye.
What's that? I'm gonna cry. It's so cute!
She said it was a story only the two of them knew.
You said we were the only two people who knew about it.
How did she know?
I didn't want her to think
I didn't want her to think I was glad we broke up.
I liked her.
You dumped me and made me the cutest girl alive.
You dumping me made me the cutest girl.
Thank you.
You're the cutest.
Cutest of all!
You're the cutest thing I've ever seen.
Say it and know it
He's getting cuter and cuter.
Listen to this.
You broke up with me and I'm the cutest thing ever.
The cutest crush I've ever had.
He's the cutest thing I've ever seen. It's the cutest thing I've ever seen.
Admit it... you're learning to be a girl.
You're the cutest thing I've ever seen
I'm the cutest thing you've ever dumped me for
I'm the cutest thing in the world right now
You dumped me and I'm the cutest
This is my dream
A girl strikes back.
I don't know if you've noticed by now, but I'll tell you.
I'm so pretty right now.
You started it and you didn't finish it.
I'm gonna cry if I hear you say that. You're so cute.
I can't believe you turned off my notifications.
I got this from a friend.
She says you contact her too much because you're a fan.
I don't care anymore.
I don't care anymore, but you just dumped me and I'm the cutest thing ever.
I've never had a crush on anyone in my life, and you're the cutest thing I've ever heard.
Admit it. This is a girl in reverse.
That's it. That's it. That's it.
By H.
As you can imagine, right after a heartbreak...
She's so cute, all messed up with tears.
You made her cry, but it was just a messy goodbye.
I'm gonna cry.
You said it was a story only you two knew.
How did she know about it?
I didn't want you to think I was glad we broke up.
I liked you.
You dumped me, and I became the cutest thing in the world.
You dumping me made me the prettiest girl alive.
In fact, thank you for being the prettiest.
You dumped me, and I became the most adorable person ever.
I told you that you made me prettier
When I heard that he'd become prettier...
You dumped me, and I'm the cutest thing in the world.
I have the biggest crush of all time
I'm the cutest It's the cutest thing I've ever seen.
Admit it... you're learning to be a girl.
You're the cutest thing I've ever seen
I'm the cutest girl ever because you dumped me.
Thank you for watching.
I'm the cutest thing in the world right now
I'm the cutest girl ever because you dumped me
This is how a girl strikes back.
I'm the cutest thing in the world right now.
I don't know if you've noticed by now, but I'm going to tell you.
I'm so pretty now.
I can't believe you started it and you didn't finish it.
I'm gonna cry if I hear that.
That's so cute!
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I told him I've been in touch with you too much... because you've been making me nervous.
I don't care anymore.
But now that you broke up with me...
You're the cutest thing I've ever seen.
I'm the most beautiful girl in the history of my life.
Look at me. Look at me.
This is a girl underwear.
I mean, you'd think that right after a heartbreak...
She's all cried out and flirty and cute.
You made her cry, but it was just a gut-wrenching goodbye.
Oh, my God, that's so cute when she cries.
You said it was a story only you two knew.
How did she know?
I didn't want her to think I was glad we broke up.
I liked you.
When you dumped me, I suddenly became cute.
When you dumped me, I was suddenly pretty at first.
Thank you.
She was pretty suddenly at first.
Tell me. Tell me.
She's become pretty. He said she's getting prettier.
Hey, listen.
When you dump me, I'm suddenly cute.
The most exciting time of my life is during the summer, when I'm suddenly pretty at first.
Admit it... this is how a girl strikes back.
She's suddenly cute at first
When you dump me, I'm suddenly cute at first
I don't know why
When I smile, it's as if the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy 'cause I can't walk otherwise
I'm sure that somewhere someone's crying, and somewhere else I'll get my body wet again
I wonder if it's cold Somewhere someone's crying
I want to share this little bit of my feelings with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart
It's guiding me
I can tell you now, I'm not sure why I'm crying
And time will remind me again soon
I'll be able to smile when it rains
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, my tears are making me
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
I'll wear a rainbow dress
lalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalala
Thank you for watching!